Afternoon
everyone.
>> Good afternoon.
>> Let's begin with some scheduling
updates. Tomorrow, President Trump will
travel to the great states of Ohio and
Kentucky where he will tout his economic
victories and detail the
administrationwide efforts to continuing
lowering prices to make everyday life
more affordable for working Americans.
The president will visit Thermoffisher
Scientific in Ohio and give remarks at
Vers Logistics in Kentucky. On Thursday,
President Trump and the First Lady will
host a Women's History Month event in
the East Room. And on Friday, the
president will sign several executive
orders, and we will provide more details
on those later this week. As President
Trump shared with the American people
last night, the United States military
is making tremendous tr strides towards
achieving our military objectives for
Operation Epic Fury. 10 days in, this
campaign has been a resounding success
thus far, and America's warriors are
winning this important fight at an even
faster pace than we anticipated. More
than 5,000 enemy targets have been
struck so far. Iran's ballistic missile
attacks are down more than 90% and their
drone attacks are down by approximately
85% since the start of Operation Epic
Fury. The United States is also
annihilating the Iranian regime's navy,
and we have destroyed more than 50
Iranian naval vessels, including a major
drone carrier ship. None of the regime's
vessels are operating in major regional
waterways, and the Iranian Navy has been
assessed as combat ineffective. The
trend is clear. US combat capabilities
are increasing and growing more lethal
and dominant by the day, while the
Iranian terrorist regime's ability to
respond has rapidly declined. Now, the
US military is moving to dismantle
Iran's missile production
infrastructure. Our incredible B2
bombers recently dropped dozens of 2,000
pound penetrator bombs on deeply buried
missile sites. Last night, President
Trump reiterated his commitment toward
keeping oil flowing through the Strait
of Hermuz so the United States and all
of our allies can receive their energy
needs. President Trump will not allow
rogue Iranian terrorists to stop the
freedom of navigation and the free flow
of energy. Let me be clear. It is a good
thing to wipe out terrorists who
indiscriminately target civilians and
attempt to hold the global economy
hostage. And President Trump could be
commend should be commended for doing
so. As the president made unequivocally
clear to the remaining elements of this
terrorist regime in his statement
yesterday, if they do anything to stop
the flow of oil or goods within the
straight of Hermuz, they will be hit by
the world's most powerful military 20
times harder than they have been hit
thus far. Moving forward, the stated
objectives for Operation Epic Fury
remain the same. Destroy the terrorist
regime's ballistic missiles. Raise their
Iranian missile industry to the ground.
ensure their terrorist proxies can no
longer destabilize the re region and
ensure that Iran never obtains a nuclear
weapon. President Trump remains
confident these goals will be
accomplished in swift fashion. As for
the oil, President Trump fully expected
the rogue Iranian regime to try and
disrupt the global markets. That's why
President Trump and his energy team have
been planning for this long before the
strike and have moved quickly to address
these temporary disruptions. Thus far,
the Trump administration has offered
political risk insurance to tankers
operating in the Gulf. The Treasury
temporarily waved certain oil related
sanctions. And the commander-in-chief
has offered the US Navy to escort
tankers when necessary. The president
and his energy team are closely watching
the markets, speaking with industry
leaders, and the US military is drawing
up additional options following the
president's directive to continue
keeping the Strait of Hermoose open. I
will not broadcast what those options
look like, but just know the president
is not afraid to use them. Rest assured
to the American people, the recent
increase in oil and gas prices is
temporary, and this operation will
result in lower gas prices in the long
term. Once the national objectives of
Operation Epic Fury are fully achieved,
Americans will see oil and gas prices
drop rapidly, potentially even lower
than they were prior to the start of the
operation, and we will live in a world
where Iran can no longer threaten the
United States or our allies with a
nuclear bomb. On another matter here at
home, President Trump is urging Congress
to pass the Save America Act, one of the
most critical pieces of legislation in
our nation's history. The Save America
Act is overwhelmingly popular with all
Americans because each provision is
rooted in common sense. The Save America
Act has five simple requirements as
requested by the President of the United
States. Number one, voters have to show
ID to cast a ballot in an American
election. Very simple. 90% of Americans,
including more than 80% of Democrat
voters, agree with this. Number two, the
Save America Act will require all voters
to show proof of citizenship in order to
register to vote in American elections.
Again, this is popular and rooted in
common sense. Only American citizens
have the right to vote in American
elections. But after Joe Biden and the
Democrats allowed tens of millions of
illegal aliens into our country, it's
more important than ever to ensure that
only American citizens are registering
to vote in our on our nation's voter
roles, and Congress needs to pass this.
Number three, the Save America Act
abolishes the incredibly unsecure
practice of universal mail and ballots,
which throw the door wide open for
fraud. Importantly, the Save America Act
maintains exceptions for Americans to
use mail and ballots like ill for
illness, disability, military, or travel
reasons. The bipartisan 2005 report of
the Commission on Federal Election
Reform, chaired by of all people, former
President Jimmy Carter and former
Secretary of State James Baker,
concluded that quote, "Absentee ballots
remain the largest source of potential
voter fraud." And it is time for
Congress to finally address this. Number
four, the Save America Act permanently
bans men from competing in women's
sports. President Trump signed a
landmark executive order upholding the
promise of Title 9 and ending this
dangerous and unfair practice. But now
it's time for co Congress to cottify
this into law. Number five, the Save
America Act bans transgender mutilation
surgery for children. Again, President
Trump signed a common sense executive
order to do this and kept his promise to
the American people. But now, Congress
needs to do the same and codify it. It's
well past time for Democrats in Congress
to stop perpetuating the radical and
false claim that you can somehow change
a child's sex. You cannot. Passing the
Save America Act is the most important
thing that Republicans and frankly
Democrats can do to strengthen election
integrity and protect our democracy.
It's what the American people elected
Republicans to do, and they must deliver
on it as soon as possible. The president
is calling on Congress to get the job
done and send this historic piece of
legislation to his desk immediately for
signature. So, with that, today I will
take your questions. Benny, thank you
for being here and why don't you start
us off.
>> Thank you, Caroline. So, my first
question is actually about the Save
America Act. So, one of the biggest um
things that the Democrats are saying,
the claims that they're making is that
the Save America Act, it would prevent
married women from voting in elections
or make it harder for them. What do you
have to say to those claims? Is there
any validity to them? And where do you
think they're they're getting this from?
>> There is zero validity to these claims.
And I'm glad that you brought them up
because you have the Democrats who have
created this myth and it has been
perpetuated unfortunately by many in the
mainstream media. Let me be very clear.
The Save America Act does not prohibit
anyone from voting with the exception of
illegal aliens. And the greatest way to
disenfranchise American citizens from
voting in American elections is to allow
illegal aliens to vote, which is what
Democrats want to do. We see it taking
place in Democrat jurisdictions at the
state and local level across this
country. So, the Save America Act
corrects that. And as far as married
women who have changed their name, if
they're already registered to vote,
they're entirely unaffected by the Save
Act. And for the small fraction of
individuals who have changed their name
or their address, they can still
register to vote. Of course, they just
have to go through their state processes
to update that documentation. And this
is something that the American people,
married women, uh, and minorities and
people all across this country who
Democrats are insultingly saying cannot
do this. They're already doing it every
day. Going to the Social Security
office, going to the DMV, and I think
it's frankly insulting that the
Democrats are saying that there are
certain groups of people in this country
who aren't smart enough to update their
documentation to allow them to vote.
Again, this is a a huge myth and thank
you for giving me the opportunity to
address it.
>> Of course. And then just one one more
question about DHS. the funding issue.
It's been three plus weeks now. Um I was
actually so I was at I was at the
airport this morning in St. Louis,
Missouri. And it was early in the
morning and one of the TSA agents, I saw
her, she was kind of tearing up. She was
crying. I asked her, I was like, "What?
Like what's what's wrong?" And she was
like, "I can't make my phone payment. My
I I can barely make my my car payment
that's coming up." I want What do you I
think a lot in the beltway there's so
much noise between Democrats,
Republicans. It's the Democrat's fault.
It's the Republicans's fault. But what
is the White House's message to the
American people that are struggling
because they're not getting that
paycheck. It's take away the politics.
What do you have to say to those people?
>> President Trump wants the Department of
Homeland Security. He wants TSA. He
wants FEMA. He wants the brave men and
women of our United States Coast Guard
to receive their paychecks. And he wants
this department to be fully funded and
fully reopened. And so to any American
out there uh who is struggling without a
paycheck, we know there's more than
100,000 of you across the country. To
any American out there who is showing up
to an airport and facing uh incredibly
long wait times and lines, call your
Democrat member of Congress and tell
them to fund the Department of Homeland
Security. That's what President Trump
wants to do. And it's completely
ridiculous that the American people are
suffering as a result of these partisan
games that are being played by Democrats
on Capitol Hill.
>> Thank you, Steve. Well, I think you said
the operation was going faster than
anticipated. What is your current
timeline for how long the war will last?
>> So, look, as you know, Steve, the
president and the US military's uh
initial timeline was about four to six
weeks to achieve the full objectives of
Operation Epic Fury. Again, to destroy
their missiles and their ability to make
them, destroy their navy, permanently
deny them nuclear weapons forever, and
to of course weaken their evil terrorist
proxies in the region. Uh we know that
the US military and our brave war
fighters are quickly and expeditiously
executing these objectives well ahead of
schedule. Uh but ultimately the
operations will end when the
commander-in-chief uh determines the
military objectives have been met, fully
realized and that Iran is in a position
of complete and unconditional surrender
whether they say it or not. And
>> does the president still want Iran's
unconditional surrender? Well, when
President Trump says uh that Iran is in
a place of unconditional surrender, he's
not claiming the Iranian regime is going
to come out and say that themselves. Uh
what the president means is that Iran's
threats will no longer be backed by a
ballistic missile arsenal that protects
them from building a nuclear bomb in
their country. Um I could make an empty
threat, but if I have no actions to back
it up, then that's it's an empty threat.
Uh and so President Trump will determine
when Iran is in a place of unconditional
surrender. uh when they no longer pose a
credible and direct threat to the United
States of America and our allies.
Adriana, thank you.
>> Um uh can you explain why the energy
secretary uh posted and it appeared to
have deleted a post on X saying that the
US Navy escorted an oil tanker uh
through this?
>> Yes, I was made aware of this post. I
haven't had a chance to talk to the
energy secretary about it directly.
However, I know the post was taken down
pretty quickly. And I can confirm that
the US Navy has not escorted a tanker or
a vessel at this time, though of course
that's an option the president has said
he will absolutely utilize if and when
necessary at the appropriate time.
>> And if this was something that was
posted erroneously, uh could it be
because of a staffer? What you know what
I guess will there be any consequences
for this? I know you still have to
consult, but generally speaking, I would
defer you to the Department of Energy to
answer that question. Okay. And if I
could just follow up really quickly, um,
in terms of oil, uh, sanctions, uh, the
president said that there would be some
sanctions, what that would be lifted,
would those be on Venezuela, Russia.
Could you give some specifics there and
then timing for that as well?
>> Sure. I know it's something that the
Treasury Department and the president's
energy team continue to discuss and they
will ultimately consult with the
president before decisions are made. I
don't have any announcements on new
sanctions or the lifting of new
sanctions for you today. Alex,
>> thank you. Uh Reuters has reported that
about 150 US uh service members have
been injured so far. Can you confirm
that number and and elaborate on that?
>> Um I can't confirm this the exact
number. I know it's within that
ballpark, but I would defer you to the
Pentagon um for a specific number of of
wounded or injured thus far. And and
then sec secondly, if if I can, um I
wanted to ask about u excuse me here
the there was a briefing on the on the
on the Capitol Hill today and some
senators came out and said they were
more convinced that than ever that there
would be US boots on the ground. Senator
Blumenthal said that. In fact, uh your
reaction to that and and any update on
President Trump's thinking about it.
>> Look, I would say that um Democrats on
Capitol Hill are clearly being quite
disingenuous. Uh three years ago uh not
a single Democrat voted uh for the
against the resolution condemning Iran
as the world's leading state sponsor of
terror. Yet now with President Trump as
commander-in-chief finally taking the
action that so many Democrats have
called on the commander-in-chief to do
for many many years to wipe out the
threat of a rogue Iranian terrorist
regime. Now all of a sudden Democrats
are playing politics with this
longstanding bipartisan policy of the
United States. uh and they 53 of them in
the house recently voted against the
resolution condemning Iran as the
world's state sponsor of terror. Uh so I
wouldn't take Democrats at their word.
As for boots on the ground, the
president has uh talked about this
repeatedly uh wisely. He does not rule
options out as commander-in-chief. So
again, I would hesitate to confirm
anything that a Democrat on Capitol Hill
says right now about the president's
thinking.
Kellen, you outlined to Steve the
military components of of what would be
involved in ending this war, but it
seems like there's a political
component, too. The president said to
Fox earlier today that he doesn't
believe the new Ayatollah can live in
peace. He made a variety of comments
suggesting that he should be involved in
picking the new Iranian leader. Is the
ending of this war also contingent on
Iran selecting a leader that the
president finds acceptable? And if so,
how is that not the definition of a
regime change war?
>> Look, as President Trump has blatantly
and frankly stated, it's obviously
within the best interest of the United
States and the West uh to no longer have
a radical uh terrorist in charge of
Iran, especially as we see their
reaction uh to Operation Epic Fury. They
had their missiles turned towards our
Gulf and Arab partners in the region. Uh
again this was a regime that chanted or
still chants death to America. We look
at the way that they are holding the
entire world hostage uh with the free
the restricting of the free flow of
energy through the strait of Hermoose.
So the president I think is making quite
an obvious comment again as for the
timeline of the military operations with
respect to Iran. Uh we have objectives
that we have laid out that the
commander-in-chief wants to see
achieved. When they are achieved uh then
it will ultimately be up to the
president to end this operation.
>> Okay. So I think you're Not exactly
addressing my question though. Is that
political objective also necessary for
the president decide to end this war?
>> Look, again, I just told you the
objectives of Operation Epic Fury. When
those objectives are met, the president
will dictate the end of these
operations, when he deems that Iran no
longer poses a credible threat to the
United States of America. And again, it
goes back to what does that
unconditional surrender look like? Uh
Iran can talk all they want and their
words will be very empty when we've
completely annihilated their navy. as we
are doing when we've taken out the
threat of their ballistic missile
capability, when we can firmly finally
ensure that they can no longer make a
nuclear bomb to threaten the United
States and our allies and our troops in
the region. And that's what President
Trump is ultimately seeking to do with
respect to this operation.
>> Jennifer,
>> there was a shooting outside of a
synagogue in Baltimore. Do you know if
the president has been briefed on that?
And do you have any more details on what
happened?
>> I don't, but we certainly will get you
more details, Jennifer. And um I don't
know if the president has briefed, but
I'll check on that when I get back to
the Oval Office after this.
>> Sure.
>> Thanks, Caroline. Um the president said
yesterday for the first time that he had
to strike Iran because he believes that
Iran was going to strike US targets
within 7 days and then he then bumped
that down later to 3 days. Where is he
getting that? Well, that's not the first
time the president has said that he
chose to launch Operation Epic Fury
because he felt as though Iran was going
to strike the United States and our
assets in the region first. Again, I
addressed this in the last briefing.
This was a feeling the president had
based on facts. Facts provided to him by
his top negotiators who had been engaged
with the Iranian regime in a good faith
effort. The Iranian regime regime was
lying, deceiving the United States of
America, clearly trying to uh continue
their nuclear program to create a bomb
that would of course threaten the United
States of America. Again, their
ballistic missile arsenal. They were
rapidly and aggressively increasing that
by the month uh to a place where uh they
would essentially build immunity for
themselves where a future president or
President Trump would not be able to
launch this incredibly successful
operation. And so the president again as
I have reiterated and he has said was
not going to sit back and allow the
Iranian regime to to uh threaten or to
attack the United States of America any
longer.
>> But there are no US leaders or Israeli
leaders who are making those same
claims. So is he making this up to
justify his decision to go to war now?
>> The president is not making anything up,
Nancy. He is looking at this every
single day based on intelligence, based
on facts, and based on intelligence that
he himself and his negotiators have uh
have consumed based on their again
negotiations with the rogue Iranian
regime over the past year. And the
president and his team tried in a good
faith way uh to to reach a diplomatic
deal through peaceful means with the
Iranian regime. And Iran chose this path
to death and destruction. Iran wanted to
attack the United States of America and
the president was not going to sit back
and allow that to happen. He was not
going to sit back and allow that to
happen and everyone in this room should
be grateful for it.
>> John,
>> thanks a lot, Caroline. Two questions
for you. One has to do with a followup
to your statement that you made at the
beginning of the briefing regarding the
Save America Act. Uh yesterday, the
Senate Majority Leader John Thoon uh
spoke on the effort to potentially have
a filibuster um broken. the rules for
the filibuster broken. He said the votes
aren't there one to nuke the filibuster
and the votes aren't there for a talking
filibuster. He says that's the reality.
What's your reaction to what Senator
said?
>> Look, I think President Trump the
urgency behind his need to pass the Save
America Act and his desire to get this
country saving legislation passed has
been made quite clear. He wants all
options on the table and he wants the
Senate to move as quickly as possible
through whatever means necessary. And
then secondly, just regarding the
president's trip tomorrow, looking
ahead, why uh Ohio and why Northern
Kentucky?
>> Well, why not? These are two great
states with great Americans.
>> He's just wanted to know why they're
chosen.
>> Great states with great Americans. The
president will be joined by lawmakers
from both states, uh, who he greatly
admires and respects and supports. Uh,
and he'll be meeting with business
owners in both of these places and
talking about the economy, which is of
course the utmost importance to him.
Thank you. Last week the energy
secretary issued a waiver for India to
get oil Russian oils during this energy
crisis.
>> Have you spoken to president about it?
What's the idea behind this?
>> Have I spoken to the president about it?
>> Yes.
>> Yes, I have spoken to the president
about it. Uh and the president and the
secretary of treasury and the whole
national security team came to this
decision because our allies in India as
you know leolite have been good actors
and have previously stopped buying
sanctioned Russian oil. So, as we work
to appease this temporary gap of oil
supply around the world because of the
Iranians, uh we have temporarily
permitted them to accept that Russian
oil. And this Russian oil was already at
sea. It was already out on the wall uh
the water. So, this short-term measure,
we don't believe it will provide
significant uh financial benefit to the
Russian government at this time.
>> I have one more question about Pakistan.
You know, Pakistan is a neighbor of Iran
and President Pakistan is also an ally
of US. President has been praising a lot
about the field marshall. Is Pakistan
providing any kind of support in this
war against Iran?
>> Um that I will have to check on with the
Pentagon and get back to you.
>> Sure.
>> Thanks. The president said yesterday
that President Putin told him he wanted
to be helpful in the Middle East. The
Kremlin put out a statement where Putin
said, quote, "I would like to reaffirm
our unwavering support for Thrron and
our solidarity with Iranian friends."
How does the president think that Russia
could be helpful if not helping Iran?
And did the president push Putin on
Russia sharing intelligence with Iran in
this war?
>> Um the president and his special envoy
Witkoff have both said that of course
they've sent a message to Russia that if
uh that was taking place, it's not
something they would be happy with and
they hope that it is not taking place.
As for further details about the
discussions between these two leaders,
I'll leave it to the president uh to
divulge any more of that conversation.
but he did confirm it yesterday and
provided you with a little bit of the
background and his view and his
perspective as he always does.
>> Luke,
>> regarding the uh missile strike on the
Iranian school, how long does the
administration expect that investigation
to take and will uh the White House or
the Department of Defense release a full
report of its findings once the
investigation is complete?
>> The Department of War will do that. The
investigation continues and as the
president said yesterday at his press
conference, he will accept the
conclusion of that investigation,
whatever it may be.
>> We'll go to the back row for some love.
Uh, sure. In the back with the with the
glasses. Caroline, regard regarding the
show, Caroline.
>> Caroline, is there you can go, but go
first.
>> Okay. Thank you.
>> Is there is there an update regarding
>> you have rough real estate back there,
so I'm sorry.
>> Is there an update regarding Cuba and
also is uh an economic deal imminent?
>> Sure. I don't have any updates on Cuba
for you today. Obviously, this is
something the administration is actively
dealing with. The president's made it
quite clear. It's his belief based on
fact that the Cuban regime is bound to
fall. The country is obviously in a very
weak place uh economically speaking. The
people are crying out for help. Uh and
the president believes and knows that
the Cuban regime wants a deal. So, as
you know, Secretary of State Rubio has
been engaged in those conversations as
directed by the president. I don't have
any updates for you today, though.
>> Thank you, Caroline. Regarding the
Shield of the Americas, the initiative
by President Trump this weekend, big
names, a lot of countries, but some
notable absences. For instance,
Colombia, which is a key ally with the
United States in terms of counter
narcotics, and President Gustav Petro
was here at the White House and he met
with President Trump. Why wasn't
Colombia invited to the Shield of the
Americas? I don't think we're seeing the
level of cooperation we quite want to
see yet from the Colombian government to
invite them to the Shield of America's
event in PAC, but we certainly uh hope
that this uh newfound organization will
expand and we can continue to invite
additional member countries. But uh
there was quite a few countries there. I
believe there were 17 countries
represented, 12 heads of state with the
president over the weekend. uh they def
signed a defense agreement with all of
our militaries uh to emphasize the need
to combat drug cartels through Latin
America in the Western Hemisphere uh and
ultimately of course to curb uh the
illegal trafficking of drugs to the
United States which is the president's
utmost priority in all of this. So it
was a great event on Saturday and we
look forward to the coalition expanding.
>> Kelly in the back
>> Caroline, thank you. Good to see you.
Uh, I want to get back to another
question that was asked earlier. It
talked about the political aspects, but
there's also the ideological
and the spiritual aspects of what Iran
has said for 47 years. Death to America,
death to Israel. And we've just finished
talking about the fact that terror has
been around the world. Iran has been the
nexus of that in so many ways. Has the
president stated clearly to the American
people why this is such an imminent
threat in order for Democrats on Capitol
Hill and Republicans and the American
people to understand how imminent the
threat was?
>> I think he has, Kelly. I mean, you've
heard from the president on an almost
daily basis over the course of the past
10 days. You've heard it from me at this
podium. You've heard it from the
secretary of war, the secretary of
state, the vice president of the United
States. You know, the president's top
cabinet and his officials have been
repeatedly explaining to the American
public uh the the threat that Iran has
posed to our country in this moment, but
of course over the course of the past 47
years and their words again chanting
death to America speak for themselves.
>> Go ahead. You can follow up.
>> Why the division uh within the American
people? I I realize that we have the
people are talking about the War Powers
Act. They're talking about all kinds of
issues, but have people forgotten just
how imminent that threat was? If they
keep saying death to America and death
to Israel, they mean it. Look, I don't
think the American people have
forgotten, but I think Democrats on
Capitol Hill, they've have not
forgotten, but they are just so plagued
uh with this resistance to President
Trump on everything that they do that
again they can't even rally behind the
common sense, bipartisan, long-standing
principle of the United States of
America, uh that Iran absolutely poses a
threat to the United States, that Iran
is the world's leading state sponsor of
terrorism. And I think that's reflected
again in their voting pattern. In 2023,
uh, every single member of the House of
Representatives, with the exception of
one, I believe the final vote was 412
to1 in 2023 for a resolution condemning
Iran as the world's state leading
sponsor of terror. And now in 20 in this
year, uh, under this president in 2026,
uh, 53 Democrats voted against that
exact same resolution with the exact
same language. I don't think that's a tr
a change in the threat that Iran has
posed to the United States. I think it's
a change in the Democrat party's
thinking and their vicious hatred for
President Trump.
>> Danny, what's the national threat level?
Following on, Kelly, what's the national
threat level right now because of this
death to America, death to Israel issue?
>> I believe the Department of Homeland
Security and the FBI have repeatedly and
continuously provided up updates on the
threat level to the homeland. I don't
want to speak on it out of turn from up
here, but of course uh the federal
government is continuing uh to
coordinate and partner with local law
enforcement agencies across the ground
to thwart uh potential threats to the
homeland. This is something the
administration obviously takes very
seriously. Uh we are thwarting threat
threats um that frankly most Americans
don't know about because they never make
headlines. But that's the great work
that the Department of Homeland Security
is doing and it emphasizes and
underscores the point of why Democrats
need to fund and reopen fully the
Department of Homeland Security right
now.
>> Danny on the Iranian school. Why did
President Trump say yesterday that Iran
may have Tomahawk missiles when there
are only three other US allies plus the
US that have those missiles and
therefore
>> look again as the president said
yesterday he will accept uh the
conclusion of this investigation by the
Department of War. I know there's been a
lot of speculation in the media about uh
who may be responsible for this. We're
not going to get ahead of the Department
of War and the conclusion of that
investigation. The president has a right
to share his opinions with the American
public, but he has said he'll accept uh
the conclusion of that investigation and
frankly we're not going to be harassed
by the New York Times who's been putting
out a lot of articles on this uh making
claims that have just not been verified
by the Department of War uh to quickly
wrap up this investigation because the
New York Times is calling on us to do
so.
>> Thank you so much. Uh Caroline, with the
DHS currently under a partial Democrat
shutdown, uh does the administration
have any specific concerns about
potential impact on homeland security or
intelligence monitoring of sleeper cells
inside the United States? And do you
have any comment on the potent on the
bombing, the two indiv individuals that
bombed New York City or tried to?
>> Yeah, it was absolutely despicable to
see that attack in New York City. I know
the FBI is investigating and the
Department of Justice and SDNY have
announced they are charging those two
individuals and alleged terrorists. and
I know they won't rest until justice is
sought in this case.
>> Daniel,
>> thank you, Caroline. Appreciate it.
Millions of Americans are filing taxes
for the first time since the president
signed the One Big Beautiful Bill Act
into law. New reports say that new IRS
data says that the average federal tax
refund is around $3,800, a little bit up
from the last period of last year. Does
the president believe that the average
federal tax refund increasing this year
could provide a little bit more economic
growth, something that he's been very
focused on as the year progresses?
>> Absolutely. And Americans are going to
start benefiting from the fruits of
President Trump and Republicans labor uh
through the passage of the one big
beautiful bill in these historic tax
cuts. We are midway through tax season.
So, just to provide an update uh from
the Treasury Department that just went
out moments ago, nearly 63 and a half
million tax returns have been processed
thus far. Uh 45% of the anticipated
total number of tax returns by April
15th. So, don't forget to file your
taxes, people. Uh and the average refund
this year is more than $3700.
Uh, and we know that more than 27.5
million uh, individuals who have filed
their tax returns thus far have claimed
at least one of President Trump's new
tax cuts. Over three and a half million
returns have claimed no tax on tips.
Over 15.5 million returns have claimed
no tax on overtime. Over 9.2 million
returns have claimed the enhanced
deduction for seniors. and over 60 uh
690,000 returns have claimed no tax on
car loan interest. And another amazing
statistic, nearly 3.5 million Trump
accounts have been opened uh for
children in our country thus far. So, we
look forward to I know the Treasury
Department continues to look forward to
seeing these checks go out the door uh
and into the pockets of hardworking
Americans. And the president will be
meeting with them himself tomorrow on
the road in both Ohio and Kentucky. and
we look forward to seeing you all there.
Thank you guys.